vape.deals 2018-08-26

# Privacy Policy | VAPE DEALS

At VAPE.DEALS, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information which is received and collected by VAPE.DEALS and how it is used.

**What information do we collect?**  
VAPE.DEALS collects information from you when you visit our site or subscribe to our daily deal alerts. When subscribing to our daily deal alerts, you will be asked to enter your: name & e-mail address. You may visit our site anonymously by not completing the registration process.

**What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information VAPE.DEALS collects from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (Showing content and information that is relevant to your account and account preferences)
  * To improve our website (We continually improve our website and features based on the information and feedback we receive from you.)
  * To improve site functionality (Your information helps us to effectively make sure VAPE.DEALS is bug-free.)
  * To send an occasional email (If you subscribed to our daily deal alerts, the email address you provide will only be used to send you information on e-cigarette discounts. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving daily deal alerts or emails,  we’ve included  unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.)

**What about CAN-SPAM compliance?**  
VAPE.DEALS has taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information.

**Do we use log files?**  
Like many other web sites, VAPE.DEALS makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes Internet Protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Do we use cookies?**  
VAPE.DEALS uses cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
VAPE.DEALS will not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential with the same respect to privacy as we outline here. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Because VAPE.DEALS values your privacy as we do our own, we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. Ever.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
VAPE.DEALS is in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older (actually 18 (21 in California), but this part is specifically related to COPPA).

**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through VAPE.DEALS and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**  
By using VAPE.DEALS, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes To Our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page and update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 05/20/2018

Page Contains Affiliate Links | [Full Transparency Statement](http://vape.deals/transparency-statement/)
